https://www.wearecollegetennis.com/privacy-policy/

ITADivisionsEventsNewsRankingsAwardsAlumniCollege Tennis Alumni NetworkITA Alumni AtlantaITA Alumni ChicagoITA Alumni ColumbusITA Alumni DCITA Alumni MiamiITA Alumni PhoenixITA Alumni AustraliaSupport College TennisAfter College NewsCoachesOfficials
Sign in
Welcome!Log into your accountyour usernameyour password
Forgot your password?Privacy Policy
Password recoveryRecover your passwordyour email
Search
Thursday, December 10, 2020About ITAAlumni Network Sign InJoin / RenewDonate NowContact Us
Sign inWelcome! Log into your accountyour usernameyour password Forgot your password? Get helpPrivacy PolicyPassword recoveryRecover your passwordyour email A password will be e-mailed to you.
ITA #WeAreCollegeTennis
ITA
Intercollegiate Tennis Association
About Us  About the ITA  Board of Directors  Committees  Advocacy  Community Service Month  Tennis for America  Convention  Classifieds  Staff Directory
Sponsors  Corporate Sponsors  Corporate MembersHalls of Fame  Men’s Hall of Fame  Women’s Hall of FameITA Media  News | Archives  Style Guide
ITA Membership  Team  Player  Corporate  Conference  USTA Sections  Associate/Professional  Alumni
Join / Renew
Donate Now
Wall of Honor
Contact the ITADivisions
College Tennis Divisions
NCAA Division I  Men          Teams    Results    Rankings    News  Women    Teams    Results    Rankings    NewsNCAA Division II  Men          Teams    Results    Rankings    News  Women    Teams    Results    Rankings    NewsNCAA Division III  Men          Teams    Results    Rankings    News  Women    Teams    Results    Rankings    News
NAIA  Men          Teams    Results    Rankings    News  Women    Teams    Results    Rankings    NewsJunior College (JUCO)   Men          Teams    Results    Rankings    News  Women    Teams    Results    Rankings    News
Live Streaming Sites
View daily scheduleEvents
ITA Events
Fall Championships  ITA Regional Small College Championships  Milwaukee Tennis Classic  Oracle ITA Masters  ITA All-American Championships  ITA Division I Regional Championships  ITA Cup  Oracle ITA National Fall Championships
Winter Championships  ITA Kickoff Weekend  DI National Men’s Team Indoors  DI National Women’s Team Indoors  DII National Men’s Team Indoors  DII National Women’s Team Indoors  DIII National Men’s Team Indoors  DIII National Women’s Team Indoors
Dual Matches  Daily listing via R2 SportsSanctioned Tournaments  Listing via R2 SportsITA Tour  Summer Circuit  National Summer Championships  Fall Circuit  Winter Circuit
ITA Championships CalendarNews
College Tennis News
ITA  Awards  Events  Rankings  Updates  News Archives Alumni SpotlightCollege On TourClassifieds
Division I  D1 Men  D1 WomenDivision II  D2 Men  D2 WomenDivision III  D3 Men  D3 Women
NAIA  NAIA Men  NAIA WomenJunior College (JUCO)  JUCO Men  JUCO Women News Archives   June 2018 – 2008
Media PartnersBehind The RacquetCracked RacquetsFanWord
View all newsRankings
Oracle/ITA Rankings
NCAA Division I  Men — R2
Women — R2
NCAA Division II  Men — R2
Women — R2
NCAA Division III  Men — R2
ITA Awards
Academic Awards  Achievement Award  All-America Teams  All-Star Team
Ann Lebedeff Leadership Award  Arthur Ashe Award  Meritorious Service Award  Regional and National Awards
Sportsmanship Awards  UTR/ITA National Player Awards  Wilson ITA Promoter of the Year
View award newsAlumniCollege Tennis Alumni NetworkITA Alumni AtlantaITA Alumni ChicagoITA Alumni ColumbusITA Alumni DCITA Alumni MiamiITA Alumni PhoenixITA Alumni AustraliaSupport College TennisAfter College NewsCoaches
Coach Member Services
Coach Resources  Coaches Homepage  Classifieds  Coaches Convention  Open Dates  Coaches Podcast  Coaching Education  ITA Rulebook  Code of Ethics
Member Area  Coaches Workspace  Directory – Coming soon
Join / Renew
Visit Coaches HomepageOfficials
Home
Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. The Intercollegiate Tennis Association (“ITA”) is committed to protecting your privacy and implementing technology that gives you a safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the ITA website and governs data collection and usage. By using the ITA website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Use of your Personal InformationThe ITA collects and uses your personal information to operate the ITA website and deliver the programs and services you have requested. The ITA may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current programs and services or of potential new programs and services that may be offered.ITA does not sell, rent or lease its membership or customer lists to third parties not associated with the ITA. Our ITA corporate members, partners, and sponsors are provided with the ITA membership database as part of their corporate membership. The ITA may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of our external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you.The ITA will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ITA or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ITA; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ITA, or the public.Security of your Personal InformationThe ITA website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to the ITA site as safe as possible.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. All financial transactions are processed through a gateway provider and your credit card number is not stored or processed directly by the ITA.Third-Party ServicesITA may use services hosted by third parties, such as Google Analytics, to assist in providing ITA services and to help ITA understand visitors’ use of the ITA website and services. These third-party services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including your IP address or cookies. If these third-party services collect information, they do so anonymously and in the aggregate to provide information helpful to ITA such as website trends, without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit the ITA website – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page.Changes to this StatementITA will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect Association and customer feedback. ITA encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ITA is protecting your information.Contact InformationITA welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ITA has not adhered to this Statement, please contact ITA. LATEST NEWSWinter Circuit Rolls Into Week Two December 9, 2020 Former USC Men’s Tennis NCAA Champ and Grand Slam Winner Dennis... December 7, 2020
Subscribe to our newsletter Email Address *
The Ultimate 2020 ITA Kickoff Weekend Mock Draft [Video] December 5, 2020 Former Binghamton Doubles Duo Working to Save Lives and Enrich Minds December 4, 2020 Load more
- Advertisement - CLASSIFIEDSNewberry College – Assistant Men’s & Women’s Tennis Coach ITA Classifieds -
December 4, 2020 John McEnroe Tennis Academy – Teaching Opening ITA Classifieds -
December 3, 2020 Load more
ABOUT USThe Intercollegiate Tennis Association (ITA) is the governing body of college tennis, overseeing men’s and women’s varsity tennis at all levels – NCAA Divisions I, II and III, NAIA and Junior/Community College.FOLLOW US
Terms of UsePrivacyAdvertisementContact Us © 2020 by Intercollegiate Tennis Association (ITA). All Rights Reserved.
